aitsl.edu.au 2015-04-30

# Privacy Policy | Australian Institute for Teaching and School Leadership

## Accessing our website and your rights

When accessing, browsing or viewing the Australian Institute for Teaching and School Leadership (AITSL) website you accept and acknowledge that they contain material or information that is the subject of copyright or other legal rights.

The material and information on our websites comes from a number of sources including our Board and Secretariat and from third parties who have given permission for the use of their material or it is material obtained under licence. Accordingly, material and information are available and published on our website and may:

  * be accessed, viewed and reproduced for the purposes of non-commercial educational or research uses provided that you agree and acknowledge that copyright and any other intellectual property rights are retained by AITSL and a copyright notice will appear on each page reproduced
  * not be used or distributed for any public or commercial purpose and
  * not be used or reproduced such that it breaches copyright or any other legal right of AITSL or its licensors, including by amendment, adaptation or translation into any other form, dimension or media.

If you are in doubt as to the use of material and information on these sites, you may request permission to use the material and information from:

**Melbourne Office (Corporate)  **  
_AITSL_    
Level 8, 440 Collins Street  
Melbourne VIC 3000  
AUSTRALIA

PO Box 299  
Collins Street West VIC 8007  
AUSTRALIA

Phone: 03 9944 1200  
Fax: 1300 880 473  
Email: [info@aitsl.edu.au](mailto:info@aitsl.edu.au)

## Disclaimer

You should also be aware that AITSL has used reasonable endeavours or may have relied on other parties for the material and information on this site. We give no warranty or guarantee that the material, information or publication accessed and viewed on our websites is accurate, complete, current, or fit for any use whatsoever. No reliance should be made by a user of any material, information or publication and you are advised to make your own assessment before its use.

AITSL does not accept any liability or responsibility for any loss or damage whatsoever suffered as a result of direct or indirect use of any material, publication or information made accessible via these websites.

AITSL provides links to professional associations/organisations and information external to AITSL. In providing such links, AITSL does not accept responsibility for, or endorse the content or condition of, any linked site.

AITSL reserves the right to vary the material, information or publication on these websites without notice.

## PRIVACY

When visiting or viewing the AITSL websites, our server makes a record of your visit and logs the following information:

  * your browser's internet address;
  * the date and time of your visit to the site;
  * the pages you accessed and documents downloaded;
  * the previous site visited;
  * the type of browser you are using; and
  * the username entered if accessing a restricted site.

If you  **do not**  wish for AITSL to collect this information, you [can opt out here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

AITSL uses this information for statistical purposes and for system administration tasks to maintain the services it provides through AITSL websites. AITSL does not attempt to identify individuals as part of its regular business practices however in the unlikely event of an investigation, AITSL, a law enforcement agency or other government agency may exercise its legal authority to inspect the server's logs.

If at any stage you provide us with your email address either as part of a message, completing a survey/questionnaire or by registering to become an Authorised User of one or more of AITSL's websites, AITSL will only use your email address to:

  * fulfil its obligations to you and to respond to any questions or requests you may have
  * contact you about material changes in the Terms and
  * comply with any applicable law or regulation or where AITSL reasonably believes such use is necessary to conform with the requirements of any applicable law or to comply with legal process served on AITSL.

We will not provide your email address to any third party mailing list without your consent.

Furthermore to the extent that AITSL does retain any Personal Information about you as a result of your use of these websites, it will deal with such Personal Information, in accordance with its Privacy Policy. The AITSL Privacy Policy reflects AITSL’s obligations under the Privacy Act (1988) and the Australian Privacy Principles.

To see the full text of AITSL’s Privacy Policy Click Here (280 KB PDF).

External sites that are linked to or from AITSL's website are generally not under our control or responsibility and you are advised to review their privacy statement.

Please direct all enquiries in relation to access and privacy to [info@aitsl.edu.au](mailto:info@aitsl.edu.au)

Page authorised by: Australian Institute for Teaching and School Leadership (AITSL) ABN 17 117 362 740
